<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Myrtle Beach Real Estate Careers</title>
    <description>Blake Sloan, a top Real Estate Agent in Myrtle Beach, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 10:32:50 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 10:32:50 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Episode! The #1 Agent Success Killer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;New PODCAST Episode, And It’s FIRE! (Packed Full Of Training!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TODAY’S TOPIC: “THE #1 SUCCESS KILLER FOR REAL ESTATE AGENTS!”.
(Video Below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this is a PHENOMENON that I have studied for YEARS &amp;amp; YEARS… And It Is Deadly For Those Seeking To Be Successful In This Business!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today We Talk About HOW “FREEDOM” IS THE #1 SUCCESS KILLER FOR REAL ESTATE AGENTS IN TODAY’S MARKET PLACE!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Talk About:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-MOST AGENTS DON’T KNOW WHAT TO DO NEXT.. SO THEY JUST FREEZE..
-THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN REACTIVE AND PROACTIVE..
-HOW “SPACE” IS THE ULTIMATE ASSASSIN OF SUCCESS WITHIN YOUR “FREEDOM”
-SAME TIME.. SAME PLACE.. EVERY DAY..
-EMPLOYEE MINDSET VERSUS AND AGENT MINDSET..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-AND OF COURSE.. MORE GREAT NUGGETS :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Just Shot A New Podcast Episode And Decided To Share The Video… WE DROP SOME GREAT NUGGETS THAT I FIGURED MAY HELP YOU, OR SOMEONE YOU KNOW!..
(THOSE ARE JUST A FEW OF THE TOPICS WE TALKED ABOUT ABOVE)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZNiSPNohnME?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this episode we talk about REAL tools that can help you get clear, and  DOMINATE in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;WHY DO AGENT’S ALWAYS HAVE A “CRISIS” THEY ARE DEALING WITH, AND EMPLOYEES REMAIN FOCUSED..&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;THE SIMPLE MULTI-MILLION DOLLAR PRODUCER SCHEDULE..&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;CREATING YOUR OWN “I.W.S.” AKA.. IDEAL WEEKLY SCHEDULE..&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;PROACTIVE GETS YOU PAID… REACTIVE CRUSHES YOUR MOMENTUM..&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;SIMPLE HACKS ON HOW TO 10X YOUR PRODUCTIVITY!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take A Listen And Let Us Know Your Thoughts….&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/number-one-agent-success-killer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/number-one-agent-success-killer.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Ways To Overcome The Sales Slump</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;TODAY’S TOPIC: “HOW TO RECOVER FROM (OR AVOID) THAT CRAPPY MONTH IN SALES!”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Have ALL Been There At Some Point… Riding That “ROLLER COASTER”… The Up’s.. The Doowwnsss… It Sucks!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today We Talk About 5 WAYS TO RECOVER FROM THAT SALES SLUMP! (AKA.. A CRAPPY MONTH OF SALES!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Talk About:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-WHO YOU NEED TO CALL FIRST TO RECOVER….
-THE FASTEST PLACE TO GET REFERRALS
-UNDERWHELMING YOUR PROSPECTS VS. OVERWHELMING YOUR PROSPECTS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-AND OF COURSE.. MORE GREAT NUGGETS :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/__2BJsEBrcA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Just Shot A New Podcast Episode And Decided To Share The Video… WE DROP SOME GREAT NUGGETS THAT I FIGURED MAY HELP YOU, OR SOMEONE YOU KNOW!..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. CALL THE OLD LEADS&lt;/strong&gt;….. THEY KNOW YOU. THEY KNOW WHO WE ARE….
Just calling to see if you had found a home yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. CALL YOUR CLOSED LEADS&lt;/strong&gt;… AND ASK FOR REFERRALS….
Do you know of anyone who may be making a move the next few months?… How is the house?… Things going better?… Etc…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. GET YOUR TOP 5 PROSPECTS IN THE CAR!!&lt;/strong&gt; IDENTIFY… WRITE DOWN… AND PUT ON A STICKY NOTE…. GET THEM IN THE CAR… GET THEM LOOKING AT HOMES.
Get them in the ether…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. SEND A GIFT TO YOUR BEST PROSPECTS&lt;/strong&gt;….
Could be a used amazon book… $3-$5. Be willing to invest $50-$100 to invest in yourself and your clients…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. FOLLOW UP.. FOLLOW UP.. FOLLOW UP&lt;/strong&gt;…. IT TAKES 17 TOUCHES BEFORE SOMEONE BECOMES FAMILIAR WITH YOU IN TODAY’S TIME…..
Differentiate, Differentiate, Differentiate
They may mean to use you, but they forget you.
You have to rewire your brain to realize that they need you. They want you. If you are doing good, follow up…
Delivering value and asking for more…
Follow up with Value… Item of Value, Market Update, Numbers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take A Listen And Let Us Know Your Thoughts….&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/5-ways-to-overcome-the-sales-slump.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/5-ways-to-overcome-the-sales-slump.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
